<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<component type="desktop">
  <id>openra.desktop</id>
  <metadata_license>CC0-1.0</metadata_license>
  <project_license>GPL-3.0</project_license>
  <name>OpenRA</name>
  <summary>Reimagining of early Westwood real-time strategy games</summary>
  <description>
    <p>
      OpenRA is a Libre/Free Real Time Strategy project that recreates and reimagines
      the classic Command &amp; Conquer titles.  The primary focus is cross-platform
      multiplayer between Windows, OS X, and Linux; however, a growing number of the
      original campaign missions are included, and there is support for skirmish games
      against AI bots.
    </p>
    <p>
      In a world where Hitler was assassinated and the Third Reich never existed,
      the Soviet Union seeks power over all of Europe. Allied against this Evil Empire,
      the free world faces a Cold War turned hot. The Red Alert mod fuses the quick
      and fun gameplay of the original C&amp;C: Red Alert, with balance improvements
      and new gameplay features inspired by modern RTS games.
    </p>
    <p>
      Join the Global Defense Initiative or the Brotherhood of Nod in our recreation of
      the classic game that started it all! The Tiberian Dawn mod modernizes the original
      Command &amp; Conquer gameplay by introducing features from later games, including
      per-factory production queues, unit veterancy, and capturable tech structures.
    </p>
    <p>
      Three great houses fight for the precious spice, melange. He who controls the spice
      controls the universe! In the Dune 2000 mod you must establish a foothold on the
      desert planet Arrakis, surviving its harsh environmental conditions while protecting
      your harvesting operations from giant sandworms and ruthless enemy factions.
    </p>
  </description>
  <screenshots>
    <screenshot type="default">
      <image>http://www.openra.net/images/appdata/modchooser.png</image>
      <caption>Mod selection screen</caption>
    </screenshot>
    <screenshot>
      <image>http://www.openra.net/images/appdata/ingame-ra.png</image>
      <caption>Red Alert mod</caption>
    </screenshot>
    <screenshot>
      <image>http://www.openra.net/images/appdata/ingame-cnc.png</image>
      <caption>Tiberian Dawn mod</caption>
    </screenshot>
    <screenshot>
      <image>http://www.openra.net/images/appdata/ingame-d2k.png</image>
      <caption>Dune 2000 Mod</caption>
    </screenshot>
    <screenshot>
      <image>http://www.openra.net/images/appdata/multiplayer.png</image>
      <caption>Multiplayer lobby in the Tiberian Dawn mod</caption>
    </screenshot>
  </screenshots>
  <url type="homepage">http://www.openra.net</url>
  <update_contact>paul_at_chote.net</update_contact>
</component>
